easyfood.ie 2018-10-09

# Privacy policy | Easy Food

**Zahra Media Group Privacy Policy**

This privacy policy sets out how Zahra Media Group uses and protects any information that you give when you use our Websites, Apps or Publishing Services

Zahra Media Group is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using our products or services, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

Zahra Media Group may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from Jan 1st 2012.

### What we collect

We may collect the following information:

  * Name and/or Job Title
  * Contact information including email address
  * Demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
  * Other information relevant to usage habits of our mobile Apps such as purchases and usage

### What we do with the information we gather  
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * We will never pass on your information to any third party without your knowledge and permission

**Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**How we track App usage**

We use traffic logs to identify which pages are being viewed on our iOS and Android Apps. This helps us analyse data about page traffic and improve our Apps in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and none of this information is tied directly to specific users.

**External Links**

Our products may contain links to other websites or Apps of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over other 3rd party websites and Apps. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**Controlling your personal information**

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please email us at info@zahramediagroup.com as soon as possible. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
